▍2026 多伦多 WTA1000 第二轮
伊埃拉 6-1 4-6 6-2 帕克斯 · 赛后场上采访
They're everywhere you go now,
走到哪里，都能看到他们，
and it just keeps getting bigger and bigger.
球迷越来越多，声势也更旺。
How good does it feel playing in front of
每次你站上球场，
this atmosphere every single time you step
都能在这样的氛围中打球，
on court?
感觉怎么样？
I am eternally grateful.
我永远心怀感激。
I mean, I just came off Washington,
我刚刚从华盛顿站走来，
so I really feel like this is a celebration.
所以这就像一场庆祝。
Thank you everybody who is here tonight.
谢谢今晚到场的每一位朋友。
Thank you
谢谢你们，
to everyone who's supporting tennis
也谢谢所有支持网球的人，
and creating atmospheres like this.
是你们创造了这样热烈的氛围。
It's really the pleasure of my life
能够经历这一切，
to experience these things.
真的是我人生中的莫大快乐。
Alex, it's been a real pleasure.
亚历克斯，今晚见到你真好。
We'll see you tomorrow. We know you'll
我们明天再见。我们知道，
joining forces with Venus
你明天将和维纳斯搭档，
when you do.
一起出战。
Cannot wait.
我们已经等不及了。
Alexandra Eala, everybody.
掌声送给伊埃拉！